<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:/history</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/history.atom"/>
  <title>DigitalOcean Status - Incident History</title>
  <updated>2019-10-30T23:05:12Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>DigitalOcean</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3156689</id>
    <published>2019-10-30T23:05:10Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-30T23:05:12Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/w4j2nj1trtsg"/>
    <title>Event Processing Delays &amp; Droplet Creates Issue</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:05&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue impacting Droplet create events and Event Processing, and these actions should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:05&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has put into place a fix and users should no longer be impacted; however, we will be monitoring this issue throughout the evening and will mark as resolved tomorrow once we've confirmed the issue is fully mitigated. We apologize for the inconvenience, and thank you for your patience and understanding throughout this process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;15:05&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified a recurrence of issues affecting Droplet create events and Event Processing in all regions, and is actively working on a fix. During this time, you may experience difficulties in creating, accessing and listing Droplets via the Cloud panel or API. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3157672</id>
    <published>2019-10-29T21:25:10Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-29T21:25:12Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/gj38s895n48k"/>
    <title>Community portal issue</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:25&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue impacting our Community portal. Access to Q&amp;A, tutorials, and other content in the Community portal should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:33&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue affecting our Community Portal and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:31&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified an issue affecting our Community portal at https://www.digitalocean.com/community/, and is actively working on a fix. During this time, you may experience errors when accessing the customer Q&amp;A, tutorials, and other Community content in this portal. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3155486</id>
    <published>2019-10-29T12:32:57Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-29T12:32:58Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/hc7t78cryhph"/>
    <title>Event Processing Delays &amp; Droplet Creates Issue</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:32&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issues impacting Droplet create events and Event Processing in all regions, and all services should now be operating normally. Please contact support if you encounter any further problems. Thank you for your patience and understanding throughout this process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;11:11&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has applied a fix and enabled the Droplet creates across all regions. You may experience intermittent difficulties in creating, accessing and listing Droplets via the Cloud panel or API. We are monitoring and investigating this further. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;08:58&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has disabled Droplet creates across all regions and continued to investigate further. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;29&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;08:23&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Droplet create events and Event Processing in all regions. During this time, you may experience difficulties in creating, accessing and listing Droplets via the Cloud panel or API. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3146113</id>
    <published>2019-10-26T10:34:41Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-26T10:34:41Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/tt9788g09p8s"/>
    <title>Cloud Support Portal issues</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;26&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;10:34&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has confirmed that the issue with the Cloud Support Portal is fixed now and access to the portal should be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;26&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;08:00&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is actively monitoring the situation with the current issue related to Cloud Support Portal . We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;26&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;07:04&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with our Cloud Support Portal and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;26&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;06:33&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with our Cloud Support Portal. During this time, users may experience issues accessing the Cloud Support Portal and customers might see delays and replies might be slow. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3142866</id>
    <published>2019-10-26T02:02:52Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-26T02:02:53Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/ldq50pyhbn0s"/>
    <title>Cloud Support Portal issues</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;26&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;02:02&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue with our Cloud Support Portal, and access to the portal should be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;25&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;11:20&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with our Cloud Support Portal and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;25&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;09:40&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with our Cloud Support Portal and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;25&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;09:11&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with our Cloud Support Portal. During this time, users may experience issues accessing the Cloud Support Portal  We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3139492</id>
    <published>2019-10-24T22:57:40Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-24T22:57:40Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/l9rrfkfrdhnd"/>
    <title>DNS issues with Managed Databases</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;24&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:57&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issues with DNS resolution of Managed Database cluster hostnames and DNS should now be resolving successfully. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;24&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:11&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issues with DNS resolution of Managed Database cluster hostnames and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;24&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;14:38&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of issues impacting DNS resolution of Managed Database cluster hostnames, and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;24&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;13:40&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is currently investigating reports of issues impacting DNS resolution of Managed Database cluster hostnames. During this time, newly created Managed Database clusters may encounter issues resolving DNS. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3130645</id>
    <published>2019-10-24T20:45:31Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-24T20:45:31Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/1z3kmlvz69v6"/>
    <title>Issues with accessing S3/RDS resources inside Droplets across all regions</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;24&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:45&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our monitoring shows no disruption to S3/RDS services for the last 24 hours, and services should be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;23&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:51&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team continues to monitor this issue. While accessibility appears to be restored, we will continue to watch the situation closely due to the long-running nature of the incident. We thank you for your patience and will post an update as soon as the issue has been fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:25&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is continuing to monitor the issue impacting accessibility to S3/RDS/ELB/EC2 resources across all regions. We continue to monitor the situation closely, and we will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;15:17&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has observed intermittent issues impacting accessibility of S3/RDS resources across several regions outside of AMS3 and FRA1, and we are now expanding this incident to include all regions at this time. The cause for these issues remains outside of our network, and we have reached out to the relevant third parties regarding this matter. We continue to monitor the situation closely, and we will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;14:00&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has determined that the cause for intermittent issues impacting accessibility of S3/RDS resources inside of Droplets in our AMS3/FRA1 regions is outside of our network. We have reached out to the relevant third parties regarding this matter, and will continue to monitor the situation closely. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;11:40&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with accessing S3/RDS resources inside Droplets in our AMS3/FRA1 region. During this time you may experience issues accessing the resources. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3129261</id>
    <published>2019-10-22T20:08:09Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-22T20:08:09Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/ltkmvn9p2xws"/>
    <title>Spaces Performance Issues in AMS3</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:08&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with Spaces performance in our AMS3 region, and Spaces should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience any problems, then please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience, and we appreciate your patience throughout this process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;01:50&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Spaces performance in our AMS3 region and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;01:31&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the Spaces performance issue in our AMS3 region, and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;01:16&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Spaces performance in our AMS3 region. During this time, you may experience issues with accessing Spaces. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3131334</id>
    <published>2019-10-22T19:28:49Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-22T19:28:50Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/zrrxj30tgydb"/>
    <title>Networking issues in FRA1</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:28&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with connectivity in our FRA1 region. Network speed and connectivity should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:21&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with connectivity in our FRA1 region and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;16:31&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the issues with connectivity in our FRA1 region. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;22&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;15:26&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating issues with connectivity in our FRA1 region. During this time you may experience some latency or loss of network connectivity to Droplets and Services in the FRA1 region. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3128734</id>
    <published>2019-10-21T22:29:58Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-21T22:29:59Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/zns0nnxrrvkf"/>
    <title>Block Storage API Issues Across Multiple Regions</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;21&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:29&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with Block Storage Volumes. API actions relating to Volumes  should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;21&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:43&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Block Storage Volumes across multiple regions and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;21&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:29&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with Block Storage across multiple regions that may result in delays or errors when calling API actions relating to Volumes. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3121870</id>
    <published>2019-10-19T17:04:42Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-19T17:04:43Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/sb6p4w9ksqlg"/>
    <title>Spaces Performance Issues in AMS3</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;17:04&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in our AMS3 region. Accessing Spaces should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;16:02&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in AMS3 region and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:51&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in our AMS3 region and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;10:56&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in AMS3 region. During this time, you may experience issues with accessing Spaces. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3121629</id>
    <published>2019-10-19T09:42:07Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-19T09:42:08Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/t3mfzm7cm1t7"/>
    <title>Spaces performance issues in AMS3</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;09:42&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in our AMS3 region. Accessing Spaces should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;19&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;09:13&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in AMS3 region and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3118604</id>
    <published>2019-10-18T13:25:09Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-18T13:25:09Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/yv9hv21br0kf"/>
    <title>Spaces performance issues in AMS3</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;18&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;13:25&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in our AMS3 region. Accessing Spaces should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;18&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:42&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in AMS3 region and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;18&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:18&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in our AMS3 region and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;18&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:07&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Object Storage and Spaces performance in AMS3 region. During this time, you may experience issues with accessing Spaces. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3095689</id>
    <published>2019-10-12T12:54:50Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-12T12:54:51Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/b2t9d3swr62p"/>
    <title>Droplet Creates Failures in SGP1</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;12&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:54&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issues with Droplet create failures in our SGP1 region, and all systems should now be operating normally.  If you continue to experience any problems, then please open a ticket with our support team right away. Thank you for your patience throughout this process, and we apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;12&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;12:19&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with Droplet create events in our SGP1 region and actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;12&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;10:04&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issues with Droplet create failures in our SGP1 region. During this time, you may experience issues with creating Droplets. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3089637</id>
    <published>2019-10-10T21:01:25Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-10T21:01:26Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/2y8x7pdjvtrz"/>
    <title>Issues with Managed Databases</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;10&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:01&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with accessing Managed Databases via the Cloud Control Panel. The Cloud Control Panel should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;10&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;18:32&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with accessing Managed Databases via the Cloud Control Panel and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;10&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;17:59&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with accessing Managed Databases via the Cloud Control Panel, and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;10&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;17:44&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with accessing Managed Databases via the Cloud Control Panel. During this time, users may experience issues loading the Databases module in their Cloud Control Panel, or with creating new Managed Databases clusters. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3085114</id>
    <published>2019-10-09T17:09:36Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-09T17:09:36Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/kkfb5fbgcrpt"/>
    <title>Issues with Droplet Creation and Event Processing</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 9&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;17:09&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issues with Droplet create events and event processing in multiple regions, and all systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience any problems, then please open a ticket with our support team right away. Thank you for your patience throughout this process, and we apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 9&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;16:17&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issues with Droplet create events and Event Processing in multiple regions and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 9&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;15:22&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Droplet create events and event processing in multiple regions. During this time you may experience delays creating Droplets via the Cloud Control Panel or API, as well as issues with other event processing such as resizing. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3079682</id>
    <published>2019-10-08T13:23:39Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-08T13:23:39Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/g4h15s1jcbmy"/>
    <title>Network Maintenance in TOR1 region</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 8&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;13:23&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Completed&lt;/strong&gt; - The scheduled maintenance has been completed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 8&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;10:01&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In progress&lt;/strong&gt; - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 8&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;05:51&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scheduled&lt;/strong&gt; - During the above window, our networking team will be making changes to our core networking equipment to improve performance and support future functionality in the TOR1 region.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expected Impact:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do not expect any impact to customer traffic during this maintenance, but there will be a risk of increased latency and packet loss while upgrades are performed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions or concerns, please reach out to us by opening up a ticket on your account.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3078887</id>
    <published>2019-10-08T00:48:16Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-08T00:48:16Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/bqd31p7jk1pt"/>
    <title>Issues with Kubernetes configuration files.</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 8&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;00:48&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with Kubernetes configuration files expiring prematurely in version 1.15-4. All clusters should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 8&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;00:15&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Kubernetes configuration files expiring prematurely in version 1.15-4 and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 7&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:34&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with Kubernetes configuration files expiring prematurely in version 1.15-4 and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 7&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:26&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with Kubernetes configuration files expiring prematurely. During this time, you may experience issues accessing your cluster. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3065652</id>
    <published>2019-10-03T22:00:49Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-03T22:00:49Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/7kwln6lgly2l"/>
    <title>Errors When Updating Managed Database Connection Pools</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 3&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:00&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issue with updating Managed Database connection pool settings. Changes made to the connection pool settings should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 3&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:08&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the errors being received when updating Managed Database connection pool settings, and is actively working on a fix. We will post an update as soon as additional information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 3&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:58&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with errors being received when updating Managed Database connection pool settings. During this time, users may experience issues updating connection pool settings. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3061356</id>
    <published>2019-10-02T20:02:49Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-02T20:02:51Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/7hjvqpg9rj5k"/>
    <title>Block Storage Issues in SFO2 region</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 2&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:02&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issues with Block Storage in the SFO2 region, and all systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience any problems, please open a ticket with our support team. Thank you for your patience and understanding throughout this incident, and we apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 2&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:19&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Block Storage in our SFO2 region and is monitoring the situation closely. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 2&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;17:48&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Block Storage in our SFO2 region. During this time you may experience higher latency with our Volume service in this region. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3057729</id>
    <published>2019-10-01T21:32:04Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-01T21:32:04Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/p0zsvfwmc9zl"/>
    <title>Support Ticket/Portal Issues</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:32&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - The backfill process has completed for users who have recently signed up and our engineering team has resolved the issue with support ticket routing. Ticket creation and submission should now be operating normally.  If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:41&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of the issue with support ticket routing and the support portal, and has implemented a fix to resolve the issue. At this time, actions are currently processing to allow users who have recently signed up to correctly submit support tickets. Our team anticipates this process to execute for the next few hours. We will post another update once the process has completed.&lt;br /&gt;If you experience any issues during this time, please submit a ticket via our contact form to work around the issue: https://www.digitalocean.com/company/contact/#support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:04&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team is investigating an issue with support ticket routing, and our support portal. At this time, users who have recently signed up with DigitalOcean may experience an error when attempting to access the support portal or submit tickets at https://cloudsupport.digitalocean.com/s/. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To work around this, users may submit tickets via our contact form here: https://www.digitalocean.com/company/contact/#support&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3054201</id>
    <published>2019-10-01T03:41:27Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-04T15:42:54Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/g76kgjxqrzxs"/>
    <title>Block Storage Issues Across All Regions</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;03:41&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issues with Block Storage. All systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;01:38&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issues with Block Storage. All systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:59&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Block Storage and Kubernetes clusters and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:27&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified an issue with Block Storage across all regions. During this time you may experience higher latency with our Volume Service. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information and will be sure to update this as individual regions come back online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:04&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified an issue with Block Storage across all regions. During this time you may experience higher latency with our Volume Service. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:55&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified an issue with Block Storage across all regions. During this time you may experience higher latency with our Volume Service. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:25&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified an issue with Block Storage across all regions. During this time you may experience higher latency with our Volume Service. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3054289</id>
    <published>2019-10-01T01:37:40Z</published>
    <updated>2019-10-01T01:37:41Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/y24w0s00jhmq"/>
    <title>Issues with Block Storage and Kubernetes</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Oct &lt;var data-var='date'&gt; 1&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;01:37&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issues with Block Storage and Kubernetes clusters. All systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience problems, please open a ticket with our support team. We apologize for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:58&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has implemented a fix to resolve the issue with Block Storage and Kubernetes clusters and is monitoring the situation. We will post an update as soon as the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:29&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of an issue with Block Storage impacting all regions and is actively working on a fix. At this time you will not be able to make use of the control panel or the API to manage your Kubernetes clusters, however, in most cases workloads that are not dependent on block storage will continue to process normally within your cluster. We will continue to update this as individual regions are back online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;23:03&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of an issue with Block Storage impacting all regions and is actively working on a fix. At this time you will not be able to make use of the control panel or the API to manage your Kubernetes clusters, however, in most cases workloads that are not dependent on block storage will continue to process normally within your cluster.+&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;22:55&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of an issue with Block Storage impacting all regions and is actively working on a fix. At this time you will not be able to make use of the control panel or the API to manage your Kubernetes clusters, however, in most cases workloads that are not dependent on block storage will continue to process normally within your cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;30&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;21:58&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has identified the cause of an issue with Block Storage impacting all regions and is actively working on a fix. At this time you will not be able to make use of the control panel or the API to manage your Kubernetes clusters, however, in most cases workloads that are not dependent on block storage will continue to process normally within your cluster.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3045652</id>
    <published>2019-09-28T20:08:10Z</published>
    <updated>2019-09-28T20:08:10Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/x56l9t6z3qm8"/>
    <title>Networking Issues in SGP1</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;28&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;20:08&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has resolved the issues impacting network performance and connectivity in our SGP1 region. Please open a ticket with our Support team if you experience any further problems. We apologize for any inconvenience, and appreciate your patience throughout this process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;28&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;18:52&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has addressed the issues impacting Network performance and connectivity in our SGP1 region and is monitoring the situation. We apologize for the inconvenience, and will post an update as soon as we've confirmed the issue is fully resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;28&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;16:20&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identified&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team has identified the cause of the issues related to Networking in our SGP1 region and is actively working on mitigating these issues. We will continue to monitor the situation very closely. We apologize for the inconvenience and will post an update as soon as more information is available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;28&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;14:17&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team continues to investigate the issues related to Networking in our SGP1 region. During this period, intermittent connectivity issues and/or latency may be experienced by customers in the region. We will provide more information as soon as it's available. Thank you for your ongoing patience and understanding throughout this process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;28&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;09:58&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating&lt;/strong&gt; - Our Engineering team is investigating an issue with Networking in our SGP1 region. During this time you may experience latency issues or connection issues in SGP1. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:status.digitalocean.com,2005:Incident/3043477</id>
    <published>2019-09-27T19:33:15Z</published>
    <updated>2019-09-27T19:33:15Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://status.digitalocean.com/incidents/yvwsxjgdjchx"/>
    <title>Service Creation Issues across all regions</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;27&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;19:33&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolved&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has resolved the issues affecting creation of new Droplets and services across all regions. All systems should now be operating normally. If you continue to experience any problems, then please open a ticket with our support team right away. We apologize for any inconvenience, and we appreciate your patience throughout this process..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Sep &lt;var data-var='date'&gt;27&lt;/var&gt;, &lt;var data-var='time'&gt;18:49&lt;/var&gt; UTC&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; - Our engineering team has observed issues affecting creation of new Droplets and services across all regions. Services impacted would include Droplet, Load Balancer, Kubernetes cluster and Managed Database creation in any region. Our Engineering team has applied a fix and we will continue to monitor the situation for any further issues. We apologize for the inconvenience and will share an update once we have confirmed that this matter can be considered resolved.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
